var questions = [{
	"question":"What is the Focal length of convex lens ?",
	"option1": "Positive",
	"option2":"Negative",
	"option3":"Zero",
	"option4":"None of the above",
	"answer":"1"
},{
	"question":"What is the Focal length of concave lens ?",
	"option1": "Positive",
	"option2":"Negative",
	"option3":"Zero",
	"option4":"None of the above",
	"answer":"2"
},{
	"question":"What is 'F' stand in lens formula ?",
	"option1": "Object distance",
	"option2":"Image distance",
	"option3":"Focal length",
	"option4":"Radius of curvature",
	"answer":"3"
},{
	"question":"What is 'V' stand in lens formula ?",
	"option1": "Image distance",
	"option2":"Object distance",
	"option3":"Focal length",
	"option4":"Radius of curvature",
	"answer":"1"
},{
	"question":"What is 'U' stand in lens formula ?",
	"option1": "Image distance",
	"option2":"Object distance",
	"option3":"Focal length",
	"option4":"Radius of curvature",
	"answer":"2"
},{
	"question":"What is 'R' stand in lens formula ?",
	"option1": "Image distance",
	"option2":"Object distance",
	"option3":"Focal length",
	"option4":"Radius of curvature",
	"answer":"4"
},{
	"question":"What is the Nature of convex lens ?",
	"option1": "Converging",
	"option2":"Diverging",
	"option3":"Don't know",
	"option4":"None of the above",
	"answer":"1"
},{
	"question":"What is the Nature of concave lens ?",
	"option1": "Converging",
	"option2":"Diverging",
	"option3":"Don't know",
	"option4":"None of the above",
	"answer":"2"
},{
	"question":"In which condition the convex lens formed image at infinite  ?",
	"option1": "U=R",
	"option2":"U=V",
	"option3":"U=F",
	"option4":"U=0",
	"answer":"3"
},{
	"question":"What is the condition  virtual image in  convex lens ?",
	"option1": "U>R",
	"option2":"F<U<R",
	"option3":"U<F",
	"option4":"None of the above",
	"answer":"3"
}]